canistream.it 2014-04-16

# Can I Stream.It?: Search Netflix, Hulu, Google Play, iTunes, and more, for movies to stream instantly, rent, and buy.

Urban Pixels, LLC, ("We" or "UP") is the owner of Can I Stream.It and is posting this Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") to inform consumers about how we handle and share information that we collect in the course of administering the services on our site. The terms "you" and "your" when used herein means any user of our website (the "Site"). 

The Information We Collect and Store When you browse our Site we may collect and store the following information about your visit, including but not limited to: your Internet domain name and IP address, the type of browser and operating system used to access our Site, the pages you visit, the date and time of your visit and your e-mail address. 

Cookies: we use "cookies" both to collect information to improve our services, and to make it convenient for you to login. We may also use "cookies" to enable certain features on our Site, to better understand how you interact with the Site and to monitor and accumulate non-identifiable usage and web traffic to the Site. 

How We Use Personal Information 

We use this information to learn about the number of people who visit our Site and to assist in making changes to our Site; in order to improve the content and services, to better understand your needs and interests and to personalize and improve your experience on our Site. Your email address and all other personally identifiable information you provide may be used to fulfill your requests and also may be used by us for other purposes related to your visit to our Site or to further our business purposes. We never share your information with Third Parties. 

Information Sharing and Disclosure 

Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement Requests; Protection of UP's Rights. UP may disclose to outside parties stored information about you that we collect when we have a good faith belief that disclosure is reasonably necessary to (A) comply with a law, regulation or compulsory legal request; (B) protect the safety of any person from death or serious bodily injury; (C) prevent fraud or abuse of the Site or its users. 

Policy toward Children 

UP's products and services are not directed to children under 18, and we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 18. Should we become aware that a child under 18 has provided us with personal information, we will take steps to delete such information from our files. 

Newsletter Communications If you sign up for our Newsletter, we may use information you have given to us, for example, to measure your interest in various services or special offers, and inform you about new products and services. These offers may be based on information you provide in your initial visit with us, through surveys, or through information we collect about the pages you visit. We never share your information with Third Parties. Any newsletters used to send you a product or service offer will be developed and managed by UP. At any time you may request to be removed from the newsletter by selecting "Unsubscribe" at the bottom of every newsletter. 

Contacting Us 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please email us: info@urbanpixels.com 

Changes to our Privacy Policy and Terms & Conditions 

As we continue to modify our Site and add new services or functionality, this Privacy Policy will most likely change. Therefore, we encourage you to refer to this Privacy Policy on an ongoing basis.
